Hello Hello friend welcome to our
YouTube channel Jyotishi Technical Uttarakhand
Technical as you know I keep
bringing technical related videos for you
today in this video I will talk to you about something related to it
click on it today
I will tell you which
insurance company is the
best for your vehicle insurance I will
give you all the information about it I will tell you the full name of that company
which insurance company is
what it is I am not a professional on YouTube
whatever problems I face
here in my workshop
I share that thing with you and
please ask me on which topic
you want a video to make I will
tell you on that topic I do
n't understand what I should tell you
because whenever any problem comes in front of me I
make some video
for you so
please ask me in the comment box
or ask me something new I will tell you that
if you are wondering which insurance company it is then don't be
clear it is not a separate new company it
is not a wonder  It is not an insurance
company nor is there any particular name for it,
I just want to tell
you that the insurance company
which is in your own city is the best for you, right,
whichever insurance company it is, whether it is from the
government sector or the private
sector, that is the best for you for your
insurance option,
I have made a complete video in my previous video,
its complete video is the
recording of complete knowledge of insurance,
so you should see what I have
mentioned in it, but people could not see,
what can I do, this much work has to be done in it,
click here,
I only and only tell you the
same thing as I told you, I have been doing it for the last
10-12 years and here I am
practically focusing on those things, I
share the same thing with you in my workshop, so
whichever insurance company is
in your own city, that same company
is the best for your pimp's insurance,
how are you, the first thing is that if
you are getting your car insured and
your car meets with an accident or there is
any damage, then its cashless
insurance company  There will be many workshops in your city as well
and there is
entertainment percentage, there are any insurance
companies and there are many
workshop dealerships in that city, this is a little bit of
castor oil from this, so first of all your
biggest problem has been solved that if there is
any work to be done on your vehicle, then that work will be done
in your city in
front of your eyes due to which you do
not have to run to some other city, if there is
work in your city then your vehicle will be in
front of your eyes and every person
wants that if there is any work to be done on my vehicle tomorrow then it is
better, the person feels satisfied
and secondly if any kind of
problem arises in your fort or there is any shortage regarding
insurance then
you do not have to take out your time and go out,
I am in my city, even if I am going to buy milk, then I go
to the insurance company,
yes brother, is it like that, tell me what general I am
telling you, take any Android, you should
check it, whatever it is, all those things will
go into your plus only if you have got insurance done from your city
So
for the insurance of your vehicle in the whole of India, that
insurance company is based in your own
city,
okay friends, so stay
with me, Jai Hind